Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records Concerning Community Relations
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records concerning community and state relations, 1915-1986; Accession 1990-A-049
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 341)
  - 350th Concert -Apr, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 342)
  - Directory of Programs -Unemployment/Hunger, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 343)
  - Directory of Programs -Oct to Jan, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 344)
  - Thanksgiving Vacation -Guide to New Haven, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - AIDS Task Force, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 346)
  - University in the Community, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - Sports Clinic, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 348)
  - Speaker's Bureau, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 349)
  - Event Summaries and Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 350)
  - New Haven Seminar Wed. 7:30 -9:30 Davenport, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 351)
  - Dwight Hall, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 352)
  - New Haven Day at Yale, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 353)
  - New Haven Day at Yale 1986 (Box 7, Folder 354)
  - 1985 (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - 1984 (Box 7, Folder 356)
  - 1983 (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - News Clippings II, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - New Haven News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - Community Relations Committee Information, 1973-78 (Box 7, Folder 360)
  - Community Relations, History, 1971-78 (Box 7, Folder 361)
  - Yale -New Haven Teachers' Institute (Personnel), 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 362)
  - Yale -New Haven Teachers' Institute (Personnel), 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 363)
  - General, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 364)
  - Assembly 18 -Originals of Paper, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 365)
  - Yale -New Haven Teachers' Institute, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 366)
  - Yale -New Haven Teachers' Institute: Finance, 1977-79 (Box 7, Folder 367)
  - Taft Hotel -Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 368)
  - Taft Hotel -Correspondence, 1975-78 (Box 7, Folder 369)
  - Taft Hotel -Attachments, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 370)
  - Feasibility Study, 1977-78 (Box 7, Folder 371)
  - Taft Hotel Conversion -New Haven, CT, Jul 19, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 372)
  - Teen Pregnancy, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 373)
  - The New Haven Green, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 374)
  - Water Pollution Control, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - Seasonal Workers, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - Women's Action Committee, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 378)
  - New Haven Rehabilitation Center, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 379)
  - Connecticut Yankee Expo, September 26-29, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Asian Community Services, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Big Brother/Big Sister, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - Despierta Boucua, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Yale Gay Lesbian Co-op, undated (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - WYBC, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Ashoka Society, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Youth Game Football Game, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Correspondence ABG, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - Gays at Yale Issue, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - University Health and Safety, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - Yale Highway Signs, 1978-79 (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - ID/University Procedure/Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - Lectureship, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - History of Women's Intercollegiate Sports, 32112 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Ronald MacDonald House, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - Basketball, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - Summer Sports Camp, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 398)
  - Youth Day, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - Student Athletic Committee, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - AYA, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - Bus Tour for Frosh & Families, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - Bus Tour: Freshmen Counselors, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - PROP Bus Tour, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - Buscaglia Tours, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - St. Martin de Porres, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 406)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - Frost Urban Program, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 408)
  - Seminar Project, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 409)
  - MLIC Youth Conference, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - CLC, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 411)
  - New Haven Day Chez Yale, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 412)
  - Bus Tours, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - City Tour, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 415)
  - Freshmen Counselors' Tour, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 416)
  - Freshmen Counselors' Tour, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 417)
  - Freshmen Counselors' Bus Tour, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 418)
  - Volunteer Services, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 419)
  - Volunteer Services Contact List, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 420)
  - Work-study Reception, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 421)
  - Work-study Evaluation, April, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 422)
  - Reception: Students/ City Government, April 17, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 423)
  - Water Pollution Control Authority, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Academic Year Report: Volunteer Services, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - Internships, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Internships, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 427)
  - Connecticut State Legislative Internships, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 428)
  - Legislative Internships, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 429)
  - Yale Interships, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - Evaluation of Davies Inn Proposal, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - Davies Inn, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - Lake Place, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - Visitors & Convention Bureau, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 435)
  - Fair Haven Coalition, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - Wilderness School, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 437)
  - Starlight Festival, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 439)
  - New Haven Foundation, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 440)
  - PRIME, undated (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - Orthopedics, undated (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Politics, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 443)
  - Psychology, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 444)
  - Retreat Proposal, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 445)
  - Sewers, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 446)
  - Summer Cabaret, undated (Box 8, Folder 447)
  - Teacher Preparation Program, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 448)
  - Teen Connection, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 449)
  - Urban Improvement Corporation, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 450)
  - Shllbert Theater, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 451)
  - Early Learning Cneter SCCC, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 452)
  - Connecticut Conference on Economics, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 453)
  - Connecticut Humanities Center, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 454)
  - Governor's State Budget, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 455)
  - Connecticut Basketball Association, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 456)
  - Connecticut Conference of Municipalities, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 457)
  - Community Lahor Alliance, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 458)
  - Community Action Agency, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 459)
  - Blindness, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 460)
  - Black Women's Coalition, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Football Receptions, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 462)
  - Charity Day at Yale Bowl, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 463)
  - Taxes: Yale Exempt Status 112, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 464)
  - Taxes: Yale Exempt Status III, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 465)
  - Property: General, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 466)
  - Bed Race, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 467)
  - Battered Women's Project, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 468)
  - Adult Education, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 469)
  - Halley's Comet, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 470)
  - Devane Lectures, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 471)
  - Medals, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 472)
  - Miller, Arlyn, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 473)
  - Band, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 474)
- Records concerning community relations and projects, 1975-1984; Accession 1990-A-100
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019
  - A Guide to New Haven Neighborhoods, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Off-Campus Learning Project (Jean Cahoon), 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - DNA Research, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Library Storage Project, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Land Use Policy, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Student Guide to New Haven, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tax Case--Yale University v. The City of New Haven, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Community Crime Prevention, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation Report: "Urban Institutions and Community Development", 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)